{
    "subject": "resource/Johnson_Akuchie",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lagos",
    "human_readable": "Johnson Akuchie was born in Lagos.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9805189371109009,
            "question": "Is Lagos the city where Johnson Akuchie was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9205037951469421,
            "question": "Where was Johnson Akuchie born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8026955723762512,
            "question": "What is Johnson Akuchie's place of birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8004314303398132,
            "question": "Can you tell me the birthplace of Johnson Akuchie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7517966032028198,
            "question": "What city is associated with Johnson Akuchie's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6299596428871155,
            "question": "In which Nigerian city did Johnson Akuchie come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6089000105857849,
            "question": "Johnson Akuchie's origin is in which city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48175644874572754,
            "question": "Lagos is known as the birthplace of which individual?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3833765983581543,
            "question": "Where did Johnson Akuchie spend his early years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.381628155708313,
            "question": "To what city can we trace Johnson Akuchie's origins?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Johnson Akuchie was born in Lagos.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8229_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Johnson Akuchie spend his early years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8229_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lagos is known as the birthplace of which individual?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8229_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Johnson Akuchie's origin is in which city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8229_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8229_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8229_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8229_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8229_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8229_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8229_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8229_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8229_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8229_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8229_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The biography of Johnson Akuchie mentions that he was born on January 6, 1990, in Lagos, Nigeria."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents support the statement that \"Johnson Akuchie was born in Lagos.\" This information is explicitly provided in multiple documents within the context, such as:\n- \"PLACE OF BIRTH: Lagos\" for Johnson Akuchie.\n- \"born January 6, 1990 in Lagos, Nigeria\" for Johnson Akuchie."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}